data = [ 
    {question: "JavaScript is ______ language.", answers: {a: "Scripting", b: "Programming", c: "Both a and b", d: "Application"}, correctAnswer: "a"}, 
    {question: "JavaScript is ______ Side scripting language.", answers: {a: "Server", b: "Client", c: "ISP", d: "Browser"}, correctAnswer: "d"}, 
    {question: "The behaviour of the document elements can be defined by", answers: {a: "Using document object", b: "Registering appropriate event handlers", c: "Using element object", d: "All of the mentioned"}, correctAnswer: "b"}, 
    {question: "The service(s) that enables networking through scripted HTTP requests is", answers: {a: "XMLHttpResponse", b: "XMLRequest", c: "XMLHttpRequest", d: "All of the mentioned"}, correctAnswer: "c"}, 
    {question: "The HTML5 specification includes", answers: {a: "Data storage", b: "Graphics APIs", c: "Other APIs for web apps", d: "All of the mentioned"}, correctAnswer: "d"}, 
    {question: "Which of the following are not advanced services?", answers: {a: "Data storage", b: "Networking", c: "XMLHttpRequest object", d: "None of the mentioned"}, correctAnswer: "d"}, 
    {question: "JavaScript code between a pair of 'script' tags are called", answers: {a: "Non-inline", b: "External", c: "Referenced", d: "Inline"}, correctAnswer: "d"}, 
    {question: "Client-side JavaScript code is embedded within HTML documents in", answers: {a: "A URL that uses the special javascript:encoding", b: "A URL that uses the special javascript:stack", c: "A URL that uses the special javascript:protocol", d: "A URL that uses the special javascript:code"}, correctAnswer: "c"}, 
    {question: "What is the programming philosophy that argues that content and behaviour should as much as possible be kept separate?", answers: {a: "Unobtrusive JavaScript", b: "Unobtrusive JavaScript", c: "Inherited JavaScript", d: "Modular JavaScript"}, correctAnswer: "a"},
    {question: "Which of the following communicates with server-side CGI scripts through HTML form submissions and can be written without the use of JavaScript?", answers: {a: "Static Web Pages", b: " Interactive Web Pages", c: "Conditional Web Pages", d: "None of the mentioned"}, correctAnswer: "b"}, 
    {question: " ______ tag is an extension to HTML that can enclose any number of JavaScript statements.", answers: {a: "SCRIPT", b: "BODY", c: "HEAD", d: "TITLE"}, correctAnswer: "a"}, 
    {question: "How does JavaScript store dates in a date object?", answers: {a: "The number of milliseconds since January 1st, 1970", b: "The number of days since January 1st, 1900", c: "The number of seconds since Netscape's public stock offering.", d: "None of the above"}, correctAnswer: "a"}, 
    {question: "What is the correct JavaScript syntax to write 'Hello World'?", answers: {a: "System.out.println('Hello World')", b: "println ('Hello World')", c: "document.write('Hello World')", d: "response.write('Hello World')"}, correctAnswer: "c"}, 
    {question: "Which of the following attribute can hold the JavaScript version?", answers: {a: " LANGUAGE", b: "SCRIPT", c: "VERSION", d: "None of the above"}, correctAnswer: "a"}, 
    {question: "Which of the following way can be used to indicate the LANGUAGE attribute?", answers: {a: "LANGUAGE='JavaScriptVersion'", b: "SCRIPT LANGUAGE='JavaScriptVersion'", c: "SCRIPT LANGUAGE='JavaScriptVersion'JavaScript statements SCRIPT", d: "SCRIPT LANGUAGE='JavaScriptVersion' JavaScript statements SCRIPT"}, correctAnswer: "c"}, 
    {question: "Inside which HTML element do we put the JavaScript?", answers: {a: "js", b: "scripting", c: "script", d: "javascript"}, correctAnswer: "c"}, 
    {question: "What is the correct syntax for referring to an external script called 'abc.js'?", answers: {a: "script href='abc.js'", b: "script name='abc.js'", c: "script src='abc.js'", d: "None of the above"}, correctAnswer: "c"}, 
    {question: "Which types of image maps can be used with JavaScript?", answers: {a: "Server-side image maps", b: "Client-side image maps", c: "Server-side image maps and Client-side image maps", d: " None of the above"}, correctAnswer: "b"}, 
    {question: "Which of the following navigator object properties is the same in both   Netscape and IE?", answers: {a: "navigator.appCodeName", b: "navigator.appName", c: "navigator.appVersion", d: "None of the above"}, correctAnswer: "a"}, 
    {question: "Which is the correct way to write a JavaScript array?", answers: {a: "var txt = new Array(1:'tim',2:'kim',3:'jim')", b: "var txt = new Array:1=('tim')2=('kim')3=('jim')", c: "var txt = new Array('tim','kim','jim')", d: "var txt = new Array='tim','kim','jim'"}, correctAnswer: "a"},
    {question: "What does the noscript tag do?", answers: {a: "Enclose text to be displayed by non-JavaScript browsers.", b: " Prevents scripts on the page from executing.", c: "Describes certain low-budget movies.", d: "None of the above"}, correctAnswer: "a"}, 
    {question: "If para1 is the DOM object for a paragraph, what is the correct syntax to change the text within the paragraph?", answers: {a: " 'New Text'?", b: "para1.value='New Text';", c: "para1.firstChild.nodeValue= 'New Text';", d: "para1.nodeValue='New Text';"}, correctAnswer: "b"}, 
    {question: "JavaScript entities start with _______ and end with _________.", answers: {a: "Semicolon, colon", b: "Semicolon, Ampersand", c: "Ampersand, colon", d: "Ampersand, semicolon"}, correctAnswer: "d"},
    {question: "Which of the following best describes JavaScript?", answers: {a: " a low-level programming language.", b: " a scripting language precompiled in the browser.", c: "a compiled scripting language.", d: "an object-oriented scripting language."}, correctAnswer: "d"}, 
    {question: "Choose the server-side JavaScript object?", answers: {a: "FileUpLoad", b: "Function", c: "File", d: " Date"}, correctAnswer: "c"}, 
    {question: "Choose the client-side JavaScript object?", answers: {a: " Database", b: "Cursor", c: "Client", d: "FileUpLoad"}, correctAnswer: "d"}, 
    {question: "Which of the following is not considered a JavaScript operator?", answers: {a: "new", b: "this", c: "delete", d: "typeof"}, correctAnswer: "b"}, 
    {question: "______method evaluates a string of JavaScript code in the context of the specified object.", answers: {a: " Eval", b: "ParseInt", c: "ParseFloat", d: "Efloat"}, correctAnswer: "a"}, 
    {question: "Which of the following event fires when the form element loses the focus: button, input, label, select, textarea?", answers: {a: "onfocus", b: "onblur", c: "onclick", d: "ondblclick"}, correctAnswer: "b"}, 
    {question: "The syntax of Eval is _______.", answers: {a: " [objectName.]eval(numeriC.", b: "[objectName.]eval(string)", c: "[EvalName.]eval(string)", d: " [EvalName.]eval(numeriC."}, correctAnswer: "b"}, 
    {question: "JavaScript is interpreted by ______.", answers: {a: "Client", b: "Server", c: "Object", d: "None of the above"}, correctAnswer: "a"},
    {question: " Using _______ statement is how you test for a specific condition.", answers: {a: "Select", b: "If", c: "Switch", d: "For"}, correctAnswer: "b"}, 
    {question: "Which of the following is the structure of an if statement?", answers: {a: "if (conditional expression is true) thenexecute this codeend if", b: " if (conditional expression is true)execute this codeend if", c: " if (conditional expression is true)   {then execute this code>->}", d: "if (conditional expression is true) then {execute this code}"}, correctAnswer: "c"}, 
    {question: "How to create a Date object in JavaScript?", answers: {a: "dateObjectName = new Date([parameters])", b: "dateObjectName.new Date([parameters])", c: "dateObjectName := new Date([parameters])", d: " dateObjectName Date([parameters])"}, correctAnswer: "a"},
    {question: "The _______ method of an Array object adds and/or removes elements from an array.", answers: {a: "Reverse", b: "Shift", c: "Slice", d: "Splice"}, correctAnswer: "d"},
    {question: " To set up the window to capture all Click events, we use which of the following statement?", answers: {a: "window.captureEvents(Event.CLICK);", b: "window.handleEvents (Event.CLICK);", c: "window.routeEvents(Event.CLICK );", d: "window.raiseEvents(Event.CLICK );"}, correctAnswer: "a"}, 
    {question: "Which tag(s) can handle mouse events in Netscape?", answers: {a: "IMG", b: "A", c: "BR", d: "None of the above"}, correctAnswer: "b"}, 
    {question: "________ is the tainted property of a window object.", answers: {a: "Pathname", b: " Protocol", c: "Defaultstatus", d: "Host"}, correctAnswer: "c"},
    {question: "To enable data tainting, the end user sets the _________ environment variable.", answers: {a: "ENABLE_TAINT", b: "MS_ENABLE_TAINT", c: "NS_ENABLE_TAINT", d: "ENABLE_TAINT_NS"}, correctAnswer: "c"}, 
    {question: "In JavaScript, _________ is an object of the target language data type that encloses an object of the source language.", answers: {a: "a wrapper", b: "a link", c: "a cursor", d: "a form"}, correctAnswer: "a"}, 
    {question: "When a JavaScript object is sent to Java, the runtime engine creates a Java wrapper of type ________.", answers: {a: "ScriptObject", b: "JSObject", c: "JavaObject", d: "Jobjec"}, correctAnswer: "b"}, 
    {question: "_______ class provides an interface for invoking JavaScript methods and examining JavaScript properties.", answers: {a: "ScriptObject", b: "JSObject", c: "JavaObject", d: "Jobject"}, correctAnswer: "b"}, 
    {question: "_________ is a wrapped Java array, accessed from within JavaScript code.", answers: {a: "JavaArray", b: "JavaClass", c: "JavaObject", d: "JavaPackage"}, correctAnswer: "a"}, 
    {question: "A ________ object is a reference to one of the classes in a Java package, such as netscape.javascript .", answers: {a: "JavaArray", b: "JavaClass", c: "JavaObject", d: "JavaPackage"}, correctAnswer: "b"}, 
    {question: "The JavaScript exception is available to the Java code as an instance of _______.", answers: {a: " netscape.javascript.JSObject", b: "netscape.javascript.JSException", c: "netscape.plugin.JSException", d: "None of the above"}, correctAnswer: "b"}, 
    {question: "To automatically open the console when a JavaScript error occurs which of the following is added to prefs.js?", answers: {a: "user_pref('javascript.console.open_on_error', false);", b: "user_pref('javascript.console.open_error', true);", c: "user_pref('javascript.console.open_error', false);", d: "user_pref('javascript.console.open_on_error', true);"}, correctAnswer: "d"},
    {question: "To open a dialog box each time an error occurs, which of the following is added to prefs.js?", answers: {a: "user_pref('javascript.classic.error_alerts', true);", b: "user_pref('javascript.classic.error_alerts', false);", c: "user_pref('javascript.console.open_on_error', true);", d: "user_pref('javascript.console.open_on_error', false);"}, correctAnswer: "a"}, 
    {question: "The syntax of a blur method in a button object is _______.", answers: {a: "Blur()", b: "Blur(contrast)", c: "Blur(value)", d: "Blur(depth)"}, correctAnswer: "a"}, 
    {question: "The syntax of capture events method for document object is _______.", answers: {a: "captureEvents()", b: "captureEvents(args eventType)", c: "captureEvents(eventType)", d: "captureEvents(eventVal)"}, correctAnswer: "c"}, 
    {question: "The syntax of close method for document object is ________.", answers: {a: "Close(doC.", b: "Close(object)", c: "Close(val)", d: "Close()"}, correctAnswer: "d"}
    ];